{
    "name": "Aiko's Flashcard Collection",
    "myCollection": [
        {
            "name": "emotions",
            "currentDeck": [
                {
                    "question": "Define sad",
                    "answer": "unhappy",
                    "studyCounter": 4,
                    "status": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Define happy",
                    "answer": "joyful",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "Define angry",
                    "answer": "frustrated",
                    "studyCounter": 1,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "Define joy",
                    "answer": "smiling",
                    "studyCounter": 3,
                    "status": true
                },
                {
                    "question": "Define annoyed",
                    "answer": "irritated",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "jobs",
            "currentDeck": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the job of a student?",
                    "answer": "study",
                    "studyCounter": 2,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the job of a professor?",
                    "answer": "teach",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "random",
            "currentDeck": [
                {
                    "question": "How many letters are in the word \"three\"?",
                    "answer": "five",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is the main UBC campus located?",
                    "answer": "Vancouver",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the business school in UBC?",
                    "answer": "sauder",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "countries",
            "currentDeck": [
                {
                    "question": "In which country is Vancouver located?",
                    "answer": "Canada",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "In which country is Bali located?",
                    "answer": "Indonesia",
                    "studyCounter": 1,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "In which continent is Singapore located in?",
                    "answer": "Asia",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "objects",
            "currentDeck": [
                {
                    "question": "What is a pen used for?",
                    "answer": "write",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is an eraser used for?",
                    "answer": "erase",
                    "studyCounter": 0,
                    "status": false
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}